<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:53:42 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kissenger - First Internet Kissing Device</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/kissenger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:53:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/kissenger/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kissenger is an innovative haptic device that simulates real-time kissing over the internet. Designed for long-distance relationships and virtual intimacy, it uses pressure sensors and actuators to replicate the sensation of a kiss, allowing users to send and receive physical affection through digital communication.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tamo Robotics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/tamorobot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 09:53:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/tamorobot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At Tamo Robotics, we believe that humans will interact with robots in a more meaningful and emotional&#xA;way in the future. Robots will be able to provide emotional comfort and support and&#xA;help people reconnect with their Happy Place.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movit</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/movit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 09:53:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/movit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Movit is a wearable gesture control wristband that allows users to control mobile and PC apps remotely using intuitive hand gestures. The wristband, embedded with an accelerometer, is lightweight, affordable, and easily integrates with various devices. Movit recognizes user-defined gestures for a more personalized experience. It features a novel signal gesture method to distinguish control gestures from natural hand movements, enabling completely hands-free operation. Movit connects to mobile phones and computers via Bluetooth Low Energy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
